<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flash replacement CA on Toniebox Hacking</title><link>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/</link><description>Recent content in Flash replacement CA on Toniebox Hacking</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CC3200</title><link>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/cc3200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/cc3200/</guid><description>CC3200 # It is recommended to flash the replacement CA to /cert/c2.der and use the hackiebox-ng bootloader with the altCA.305 patch. This will allow you to switch between the original and your replacement certificate. If you have installed the HackieboxNG Bootloader and the Hackiebox CFW you may upload the certificate via the webinterface of the CFW. Otherwise you can use the cc3200tool for this task.
Flash c2.der via Hackiebox # First of all please boot the Hackiebox CFW, which should be in cfw1, so blue 1.</description></item><item><title>CC3235</title><link>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/cc3235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/cc3235/</guid><description>CC3235 # Replace the original CA within your flash dump with the replacement CA and reflash it to your box. I recommend flashrom for that
cc3200tool -if cc32xx-flash.bin -of cc32xx-flash.customca.bin -d cc32xx write_file customca.der /cert/ca.der Please continue with DNS step for the CC3235</description></item><item><title>ESP32</title><link>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/esp32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonies-wiki.revvox.de/docs/tools/teddycloud/setup/flash-ca/esp32/</guid><description>ESP32 # Browser based # With teddyCloud you can also write a new image with your custom CA and a hostname/IP so the box connects to teddyCloud. If you have a Fritzbox you can set it to tc.fritz.box (see CC3200 how to configure the hostname on your Fritzbox), if not set it to the IP of teddyCloud.
Check, that your backup of your flash is okay and you were able to extract the certificates.</description></item></channel></rss>